http://www.maui-rentals.com/global/en/terms-and-conditions

Rentals NZBritz CampervansMighty CampersMaui MotorhomesRentals AUMaui AustraliaBritz Campervans and 4WDsMighty CampersRentals USARoadbear RV RentalsBritz CampervansEl Monte RVBuy a MotorhomeRV Super Centre NZRV Sales Centre AURentals UKJust Go Motorhomes
maui Australiamaui New Zealandmaui Southern AfricaBook
+800 200 80801 View all International numbers
Choose your destinationChoose your destinationNew ZealandAustralia
Book your Motorhome Pick Up Date Pick Up Date
Pick Up Date is required*
Drop Off Date Drop Off Date
Drop Off Date is required*
Pick Up Location Pick Up Location AucklandChristchurchQueenstownCambridgeWaihiFoxton BeachWellingtonPictonNelsonGreymouthDunedinInvercargill AdelaideAlice SpringsBrisbaneBroomeCairnsDarwinHobartMelbournePerthSydney
Pick Up Location is required*Drop Off LocationDrop Off Location AucklandChristchurchQueenstown AdelaideAlice SpringsBrisbaneBroomeCairnsDarwinHobartMelbournePerthSydney
Drop Off Location is required* Passengers Passengers
Adults 123456 Children 012345
Drivers LicenceDrivers Licence AustraliaCanadaChinaDenmarkFranceGermanyNetherlandsNew ZealandSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomUnited States of America--------------------AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndoraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua & BarbadosArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiButanCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCental African RepublicChadChileChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDjiboutiIDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrance, MetropolitanFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Souther TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanamarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSeychellesSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbardand Jan Mayen IslandsSyriaTahitiTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezualaVietnamVirgin Islands (GB)Virgin Islands (US)Wallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe Drivers Licence is required* Promo
Search
Book
+800 200 80801 View all International numbers
Home Terms and Conditions
Share
Acceptance
Tourism Holdings Limited welcomes you to maui. This site is owned by Tourism Holdings Limited ("we", "us" and "our"). By accessing this website you agree to the terms of access listed below.
General Disclaimer
The content on this site is intended to provide information only. While we try to ensure that the content of this site is free from error, we do not warrant its accuracy, adequacy or completeness or its suitability for your intended use.
How We Use Your Information
When transmitting your personal information over the Internet, you should remember that the Internet is not a secure environment. Any personal information you transmit to us may be used by us to provide information to you about the full range of products and services offered by us and our related companies, as well as to assist us to create a statistical picture of our customers.
We do not sell, publish or give away your information. Information about you provided to us can be used by us and our related companies and our suppliers to carry out our business. Our Privacy Statement will apply to any personal information that you may supply.
Booking and Quoting Information
Where you wish to make a booking or receive a quotation in respect of any booking, separate terms and conditions will apply. Click here to access the Booking Conditions and General Information for Australia, New Zealand and Southern Africa.
Liability
We disclaim, to the extent permitted by law, all liability or responsibility to anyone for any direct or indirect loss or damage that may result from any advice, opinion, information, representation or omission, whether negligent or otherwise, contained on this website.
Changes to Content
All content on this website (including these terms of access) is subject to change at any time and without notice.
Jurisdiction
Unless otherwise specified, the content on this site has been prepared in accordance with New Zealand or Australian law for the supply of products and services to persons resident respectively in New Zealand or Australia only. The content of this website and any contracts formed with us arising out of this site are governed by, and are to be interpreted in accordance with the respective New Zealand or Australian law and the respective New Zealand or Australian courts have jurisdiction.
Links
Please contact us for prior permission if you wish to create a hypertext link to any page on this site. If you create a link to Maui, you remain fully responsible for any consequences of that link, whether direct or indirect and you will protect us against all loss, damage, liability, costs or expense arising from or in connection with the link. Any link to third party websites are provided for convenience only and the inclusion of any link does not imply any endorsement or verification by us. The websites linked to this site are not under our control. We accept no responsibility or liability in relation to any content on other websites that are not under our direct control.
Copyright
The content of our site is protected by copyright and no part of our site may be reproduced or adapted in whole or in part without our prior consent.
2006 All rights in this site are owned by Tourism Holdings Limited.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about these terms of access, please contact us.
Join thousands of RV travellersSign up for our Go By Camper newsletter to receive inspirational travel content and awesome deals, and we'll send you a copy of our Ultimate RV guide! Please enter your first name* Please enter your email address*Yes! I’d love maui and Go By Camper to send me occasional emails with inspirational travel content and subscriber exclusive deals.Required*Travelling soon?Sign up nowmaui is committed to protecting your privacy and information security. Your information will be used in accordance with any application privacy law, our internal policies, and our Privacy Policy, and will be held securely.ThanksPlease confirm subscription in your email.
Tourism Holdings LimitedMaui RentalsBrtiz CampervansMighty CampervansRV SuperCenterKEA MotorhomesRoadbear RVEl MonteJust GoMighwaySee all THL brandsCopyright © 2020 THLTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyMediaTravel Agents
Book your motorhome here
Choose your destinationChoose your destinationNew ZealandAustralia
Book your Motorhome
Pick Up Date Pick Up Date
Pick Up Date is required*
Drop Off Date Drop Off Date
Drop Off Date is required*
Pick Up Location Pick Up Location AucklandChristchurchQueenstownCambridgeWaihiFoxton BeachWellingtonPictonNelsonGreymouthDunedinInvercargill AdelaideAlice SpringsBrisbaneBroomeCairnsDarwinHobartMelbournePerthSydney
Pick Up Location is required*Drop Off LocationDrop Off Location AucklandChristchurchQueenstown AdelaideAlice SpringsBrisbaneBroomeCairnsDarwinHobartMelbournePerthSydney
Drop Off Location is required*
Passengers Passengers
Adults 123456 Children 012345
Drivers LicenceDrivers Licence AustraliaCanadaChinaDenmarkFranceGermanyNetherlandsNew ZealandSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomUnited States of America--------------------AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndoraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua & BarbadosArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiButanCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCental African RepublicChadChileChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDjiboutiIDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrance, MetropolitanFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Souther TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanamarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSeychellesSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbardand Jan Mayen IslandsSyriaTahitiTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezualaVietnamVirgin Islands (GB)Virgin Islands (US)Wallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe Drivers Licence is required* Promo
Search
maui Australiamaui New Zealandmaui Southern AfricaNeed help?International Numbers International - Maui+800 200 80801Call
Need Help FAQsLive Chat Contact UsClose
